[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1953, several European countries ratified this convention to protect some sorts of cheese from conterfeiting.", "correct_answer": "The Stresa Convention", "incorrect_answers": ["The Swiss Convention", "The Milan Convention", "The Geneva Convention"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As well as oranges, carrots come in white and pink varieties.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Filipino word pangalan means name in English. What does the word pangngalan mean?", "correct_answer": "noun", "incorrect_answers": ["address", "adjective", "verb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does General Grievous call Obi Wan Kenobi?", "correct_answer": "The Negotiator", "incorrect_answers": ["The Diplomat", "The Warrior", "The Powerful"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Uranus has only 10 moons.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word absinthe comes from ancient Greek and means this.", "correct_answer": "Undrinkable", "incorrect_answers": ["Magical", "Hallucinogenic", "Tasty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Moon is taken into consideration when calculating the day of this religious celebration.", "correct_answer": "Easter", "incorrect_answers": ["Thanksgiving", "Memorial Day", "Christmas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cowboy song, performed by this cowboy/actor/singer/businessman, is heard when the male protagonist of the movie Sleepless in Seattle gets back to dating.", "correct_answer": "Gene Autry", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Mix", "Roy Rogers", "John Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Methuselah, a Great Basin Bristlecone tree located in the Inyo National Forest in California, is remarkable for what reason?", "correct_answer": "It is the oldest known living organism.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is the most publicized living organism.", "It is the tallest known living organism.", "It is the largest living organism."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who killed Achilles according to Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Paris aided by Apollo", "incorrect_answers": ["Hector aided by the Nereids", "Priam aided by Paris", "Peleus aided by Thetis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Darwin and this US president were born on the same day of the same year.", "correct_answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackson", "Andrew Johnson", "Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the location of the final battle of the First Indo-China War between France and Vietnam?", "correct_answer": "Dien Bien Phu", "incorrect_answers": ["Dien Thu", "Dien Tet Hue", "Dien Phu Wei"]}]